CONTACT ME

07710482941

✓ finns.anderson@gmail.com

Pristol, UK

https://finnanderson.github.io

in LinkedIn.com/in/finnanderson7

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Computer science

Strong understanding of a range of languages including C, MATLAB, python, CSS, html.

Machine learning understanding

Machine learning understanding using Scikit-learn for data-analysis and predictive modelling.

Engineering design

Proficiency in Autodesk CAD software, CFD and FEA.

RC software

Proficiency in using RC software to encode and decode data using, microcontrollers to make intime adjustments to electrical components.

OTHER INTERESTS

Track cycling

Silver medalist at the 2018 School Games National Team Pursuit Top 10 at National School Games Individual Sprint

Intelligent Automation

I am fascinated by the disruption due to the cumulative impact of advances in mobile, cloud computing, EDGE and data science technologies.

Finn Anderson-Grout

Aerospace Engineering Undergraduate

A penultimate year Aerospace Engineering undergraduate seeking an internship in consultancy. Over the past 2 years I have worked on three projects involving engineering design, business strategy and data science consultancy.

I want to pursue a career in aerospace and automotive business strategy, to be part of a greener future. Ultimately, to work in an open and inclusive environment to build on my experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Science Consultant

180 Degrees consulting • Bristol • 10/2021 - Present

At 180DC, I am working with Pertiwi, a charitable foundation in Malaysia, to analyse their client basis using data science.

From initial business model analysis, we see the potential for significant efficiency improvements by developing a central database to store client data.

We are analysing their data to segment their customers, targeting them more effectively. In addition, we aim to use the intelligence gained to raise Pertiwi's social media presence, a crucial element of the charity's fund-raising operations.

Student Intern, Research

Bristol composites institute (ACCIS) • Bristol • 06/2021 - 08/2021

As a research intern, I investigated current composite forming processes to then design an exclusive forming platform, successfully commissioned by ACCIS to improve predictive modelling analysis.

From regular meetings with suppliers and supervisors I was able to develop an optimum product between what is available and what is desired within budget.

I was able to develop an understanding of engineering product processes, and experience presenting to the board.

A detailed report is available at: https://finnanderson.github.io/forming_rig.html

Student Intern

Laing O'Rourke • Brighton • 06/2018 – 07/2018

Working as a student intern, I had exposure to engineering business strategies to develop an understanding of the business process.

EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS

Aerospace engineering (MEng)

University of Bristol, Bristol 2023 gradation, Year 1: 67%, Year 2: 71%

Certifications: Udemy data science using python